So, Death Gun was in Laughing
Coffin, and you guys fought before.
Kirito, I need to know something.
It's about the people you killed.
How did you get over what you did?
How are you not affected by it?
How are you so strong
you're not controlled by it?
I haven't gotten over it. What?
Last night, I kept having nightmares
about the three guys I killed.
I hardly slept at all.
I saw their faces right
before they vanished.
I heard their voices.
Their words.
I don't think I'm ever
going to forget them.
But then...
What am I supposed to do?
I...
I can't...
It's okay.
I think that's probably how it should be.
I get it now.
There are things I shouldn't forget.
What it means to kill.
The significance of taking life.
And once I accept it, maybe then
I'll be able to find some closure.
That's how I see it.
Closure?
Are you accepting it?
I'm not sure what will happen
when I'm going to be a little bit.
I'm not sure what I'm going to do.
I'm not sure what
I'm going
to do.
Believe it,
the shodonga hajimari
no oto ni kawarul Yuna.
It's hard to believe
that under that cloak,
there's a real-life person
who just wants to kill.
Yeah.
And if I knew his handle in SAO,
I'd be able to figure out his name
and address in the real world.
That's the reason why I logged into GGO.
Oh.
Then, maybe his reason for being
here is because he likes to PK.
Maybe he misses the rush of
doing it from SAO. You think?
Nah, there's more to it than that.
He killed Zekseed and Tarako in
front of a bunch of witnesses.
It was the same with Pale Rider.
He always picks times when
he's got the biggest audience.
And that sign of the cross he makes?
I bet he does it to freak out
as many people as possible.
He wants you to believe he's got the
power to kill you from in the game,
but it's all a show.
If that's true, then
how's he killing people?
It's not because of brain
damage from their headgear.
The authorities said that Zexeed
and Tarako died of heart failure.
Heart failure?
My god.
To be honest, I have no idea
how he killed him either.
But the thought of firing a gun in the
virtual world and stopping a player's heart?
There's no way that's possible.
Hang on a second.
Come to think of it. What?
That was weird. What was?
Back there in the ruins.
He had his handgun out for you, but
he switched to the rifle for me.
But he kills with the handgun.
He could have killed me with it.
So why'd he switch?
Yeah, good question.
Could it be that he didn't shoot me with
it because he couldn't shoot me with it?
The handgun.
Can't use it, though. The switch.
The crossing-himself thing.
Invisibility cloak. Conditions. Rules.
Phew.
I can't tell you how relieved I
am to hear you put it into words.
Knew it.
In-game guns can't kill IRL.
Shooting someone from in
here is not what does it.
It takes preparation.
Now you lost me.
The only way to make it look
like he's killing people in
-game is by setting up for the
murder in the real world first.
How would he set something like that up?
I mean, if you're right, he'd have to get
a player's real-life information to do it.
All that stuff's secure, though.
No.
If someone's clever enough, they can
find out a player's address easy. How?
The terminals.
At the governor's office.
Yes.
You have to plug your real name
and address into him to compete.
It's an open space.
You don't have any privacy there.
No way.
You saying he peeked over their
shoulders while they entered their info?
That can't be it, because you'd
notice someone lurking next to you.
He could have used a scope or some
binoculars from across the room.
That's breaking etiquette.
He'd get his ass kicked
out of the game for that.
Then how about this
maybe death gun can like
use his cloak to turn
invisible in town too?
He'd be right there and you wouldn't
even know it but still he can't do
anything in The real world when he's logged
in here he's unconscious there right?
Wait. That's it? Yeah.
It's not just him.
Death Gun has a partner.
Check it out.
One of them plays as the Death Gun avatar.
His job is to shoot the target.
At the same time in the real world, the
second person's in the target's apartment.
His job is to take the player out.
Okay, but let's say they
found out your address.
What about the other people living there?
And they'd need a key.
As far as Zexeed and Tarako go,
they lived alone, and their
apartments were in older buildings.
The E-locks on their doors were
probably first-gen, not very secure.
Besides,
they were both diving in
GGO during the break-in,
so they were both unconscious
and completely helpless.
They couldn't hear, so the killer
could take his time getting in.
But then, you said the cause of death
for both was heart failure, right?
So how'd they stop someone's
heart in a way both
the cops and the coroner
couldn't figure out?
Maybe by injecting some
kind of drug or something?
That's one way.
Okay, but someone should
have found evidence of it.
A mark or something.
They didn't find the bodies for a
while, so they were pretty decomposed.
Besides, a hardcore gamer can go
for days without eating or sleeping.
I doubt anyone would think it's weird if
someone died of a heart attack after that.
They're crazy!
Right?
I mean, why else would anyone do this?
Maybe.
Or maybe they do it because red
players are who they really are.
I mean, deep down, I think
I'm really a swordsman.
When you put it that way,
I can sort of understand.
There's times when I
think I'm a real sniper.
Not a gamer.
Wait, do you think the guy doing
the killings is a red player too?
You know, like Death Gun?
Yeah, they were probably in
Laughing Coffin together.
I'm still wondering how
they coordinated the
killings between this
world and the real one.
How were they so precise about it?
Yeah, that's it.
That's what doing the Sign
of the Cross is about.
It's not just for show.
It's also a great opportunity
to sneak a peek at his watch.
You're right.
Sinon, do you live alone?
Yeah, but I'm sure I locked my door.
My building's got first-gen
locks, but I've also got a chain.
I think I left the chain off tonight.
Oh, man.
Listen, you're not gonna like this.
When Death Gun was chasing us on that
horse, I wasn't the one he was shooting at.
And that could only mean they got their
next victim all set up and ready to go.
Okay, then who's next?
I got a feeling that right
now in the real world,
Death Gun's partner's in your place.
He's watching the live stream, waiting
for when you get shot by that gun.
It's just a hunch.
No! No!
No, not that! Oh, God!
Calm down.
If you log out now, you'll be in danger.
Just calm down.
Go easy.
Until Death Gun shoots you, the guy in your
place isn't going to do anything, okay?
That's the rule they
set up for themselves.
But if you log out now and wake up
with his partner there, he'll kill you.
So you have to calm down.
But, but, I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
Jeez, Chris Head.
Took you long enough.
Sorry, guys.
I booked it over here as fast
as I could for my save point.
If there were a speed limit in ALO, my
license would have gotten suspended.
Huh?
What is going on?
I'd be happy to explain in detail, but I
should warn you, it might take a while.
To tell the truth, I'm not
100 % sure where to begin.
Oh, don't even.
Not to worry.
I know just where to start.
On November 9th, in Gun Gale Online,
a player called Death Gun fired his weapon
at an avatar appearing on a monitor.
That same day, in Nakano Ward, the
player of that avatar mysteriously died.
Young lady, that was unbelievable.
Gathering all that information
and connecting it so quickly,
you must be quite the researcher.
Have you ever thought about
a career in the VR section?
Whoa, you win. I'm sorry.
I'm not going to stonewall you, promise.
Just complimenting her is all.
She's right, though.
It's true.
Yo, Chris Heider, whatever.
I hear you're the one that hired
Kirito to dive into that game.
So let me get this straight.
You got him to convert
over knowing a player
got shot in-game and
died IRL because of it?
Easy, Klein, I can explain.
That's not how the player died.
Then how?
It's not the Amusphere rig.
No matter what happens to you
in-game, it can't hurt you.
And it certainly can't
stop a player's heart
when it's not even
directly connected to it.
As a matter of fact,
Kirito and I met last week to talk about
it and pretty much
agreed it was impossible.
There's no way anyone can kill a person
in real life by shooting them in the game.
Okay, then.
If what you say is true, how come you had
my brother dive into GGO for you, huh?
You had a hunch something was wrong.
Scratch that.
You know something's wrong.
That Death Gun guy's a part of it.
And I bet you sent my brother
in to try to find him.
Chris Height, we figured it out.
Death Gun is an SAO survivor just like us.
But unlike us,
he was a red player who was in a guild
of killers called Laughing Coffin.
You sure he was with them?
Yes.
None of us can remember his name, though.
Klein and I met him once, when
our group went to capture his.
Um, hey, Asuna.
I get the feeling Chris Height
knows more than he's letting on.
No offense, Chris Height,
but all we know is you work for the
government doing something with networks.
and that you play ALO as part of some
kind of research you're doing on VR Miss.
Only for the past year.
The job I had before was
a little... different.
I used to be part of the task
force for the SAO incident.
But even though we were called a task force,
in the end, we were pretty ineffective.
Chris Height, you're obviously
well-connected, and with a little digging,
you could find out what the real-life
name and address of this death gun is.
Just make a list of the handles of all
the surviving Laughing Coffin members,
then contact their ISPs,
ask which one's playing GGO now?
and trace their location.
No, sorry, that's not possible.
The ISPs aren't going to
give out a player's real
-life info if all we have
to go on are their handles.
Maybe if we ask the game's
admins, they could help.
They might, but GGO's
admins are in the U .S.,
so it'll be a while
before we got an answer.
I know my brother.
And right now, he's risking
his life in that game,
trying to find out who this person is.
When he came home last night, he had this
look on his face, like he'd seen a ghost.
He must have bumped into the guy
yesterday during the prelims.
I bet that's when he realized someone
from Laughing Coffin was in GGO.
Someone who figured out how to
kill players for real again.
My brother went back to put
an end to that nightmare.
To find out his name and stop
his PK-ing once and for all.
Darn it, Kirito.
You should have said something.
Why?
Why do you always do this?
That damn idiot.
Why didn't he say anything?
I could be backing him up right now.
All he had to do was ask and I
would have converted over too.
We all would have.
Don't you see?
That's why he didn't tell us.
If he thought there was any real
danger in what he was doing,
There's no way he'd get
us mixed up in it, too.
That's just how he is.
Yeah, you're right.
He always thinks of others before himself.
In fact, he's probably
protecting someone right now.
And whoever that is, I bet it's
someone who doesn't like him much.
Okay, Chris Head, where
is Kirito diving from?
I know you know, so
you better tell me now.
That's confidential.
Okay, okay.
I'll tell you.
I set up the room myself, so he's safe.
Security's rock solid, and the
monitoring's top of the line.
I've got a trained professional
right by his side at all times,
and I guarantee that his body's
in no danger whatsoever of…
Where is he?
A hospital.
It's in Ocho no Miss, in
Chiyoda Ward. He's in Chiyoda?
Wait, is that the same hospital he
was in during his rehabilitation?
Yes, that's the one.
I'm going over there.
I want to see him, and you
can't do a thing about it.
Tell me you got a plan.
We're going to take out Death Gun.
Once we do, his real-world
partner will stand down.
Then he'll just leave your apartment.
Okay, but he's skilled.
Black Star or no Black Star.
You saw, he dodged Hecate's bullet
from just a hundred meters away.
And besides, I can't hide in
this cave forever, you know?
By now, the other players probably
figured out the two of us are in here.
We might as well be sitting ducks.
It's just a matter of time before
someone tosses a grenade in.
You're right.
We've been a team this
whole time anyway, right?
Might as well finish it together.
Okay, but there's still the risk
he shoots you with that gun.
Oh, that thing?
It's just an old-school
single-action sidearm.
He can fire it all he
wants, but I got you there.
Just deflect the bullets with your sword.
Right, and I won't let a
single one of them hit you.
I still don't feel good about
you being out there, though.
I mean, Death Gun's dangerous, and
you shouldn't get too close to him.
Oh, come on. Hang on.
I'm totally cool with you fighting with
me, and I wouldn't have it any other way.
But, Sinon, you're a sniper, remember?
Isn't your specialty
the long-range attack?
Well, yeah.
What about it?
Here's the plan.
On the next scan, I'm going to
step outside so it picks me up.
That way, we'll get
Death Gun to come to us.
He'll probably keep his
distance and take cover.
Then he'll try to pick
me off with his rifle.
When he shoots, we'll know where
he is, and then you take him out.
What do you think?
Are you cool with playing
the decoy? Mm-hmm.
Alright, we do it your way then.
Just be careful out there,
cause if he drops you with his
first shot, I'm gonna be pissed.
I'll keep that in mind.
Wait, I just remembered.
His rifle's got a silencer and you won't
see the bullet line on the first shot.
Oh, I'll just predict the prediction.
You know, like a certain
no-good faker told -
Um, I think we should stop talking.
Oh, crap.
We should have been paying more attention.
What is it?
And will it kill us?
It's a live stream camera.
Usually, they're only supposed to
shadow players on the battlefield.
I guess this one's in here now, because
there aren't many of us left out there.
Then do you think it hurt us?
Not a chance.
For it to pick us up, we'd have to
be shouting at the top of our lungs.
Wave to the audience.
Unless you got someone back at
home you don't want seeing this.
Uh, I, um, shouldn't you
be worried who's watching?
I mean, since I sort of look like
a girl, they might, you know,
think you're, you know.
Well, I don't care.
They can think what they want.
The guys in this game are dorks.
If they think I'm gay, at least they'll
stop hitting on me every five seconds.
How much longer am I going to have
to keep pretending to be a girl?
Oh, you poor baby.
You've been faking it like
a champ since you logged in.
Another hour or two won't matter.
Thank God.
We better get ready.
We got two minutes
before the next SAT scan.
I'll set up here.
When you get outside, fire up your terminal
and let me know when our boy's close.
Wait. Hold on.
Why? What's wrong?
It's too late to change the plan now.
No.
I don't want to change anything.
It's something else.
I was just thinking about
Death Gun's real handle here.
The only name you didn't recognize
who's still alive is Sterben.
Oh, huh.
I guess that's him then.
I wonder why he gave
himself that name, though.
If I get up close and personal,
I'll be sure to ask him for you.
Well, here goes nothing.
Be careful, okay?
I would like to be strong, strong.
I would like to say that
the sadness will be.
I never felt like
it
was a long time. I was
not lost in the past.
I was not lost in the past.
I could have been a long time.
I can't see anything you can see.
I can't see anything that's all?
I can't see anything else.
I can't see anything alone.
If I can't see anything else?
I don't need anything else. Oh.